That's it.
Thank you so much!
Something kinda surprising just happened.
Alright, so from here on, I wanna share some messages from our listeners!
First up, we got a message from Happy Name AR!
Thank you!
Hey Dare-chan, good evening!
Good evening!
I'm a fan from overseas and I'm studying Japanese.
I look forward to hearing Sayuri-san's voice every week.
I really love your radio show and the fun segments.
Thank you.
As a grad student in a doctoral program, I'm researching new cancer treatments and drugs using AI.
This research is super rewarding and I'm really enjoying it.
I have something I'd like to ask Sayuri-san.
If you were to go to university after high school, what field would you want to study?
That's what they asked!
Thank you so much!
Wow, that's amazing! And from overseas, thank you!
For listening!
I'm so happy!
So, is it okay?
Am I speaking proper Japanese, I wonder?
You don't have to remember words like 'yabai', you know.
Yeah, you don't need to remember phrases like 'yabai' or 'yabai jan'.
But, um,
Keep up the good work!
I'm rooting for you!
Wow, using AI for cancer treatments and drugs!
That's incredible!
Well, I actually didn't go to university, but when I was in my first and second year of high school, I was like,
I was interested in going to a university for psychology. My future dreams were still kinda vague back then, I wasn't dead set on one thing. But yeah, I really wanted to be a school counselor!
Yeah, I was interested around my first and second year of high school. When you look up school counselors, it always says you need to study psychology or related fields. So I vaguely thought it'd be cool to study something like that back then.
But you never know, right?
Even if you decide to become a school counselor and go into psychology, you might suddenly find another path interesting while you're in university. I know a lot of people around me who were thinking of going into psychology. I feel like psychology is a pretty broad field.
At least when I looked into it.
Yeah.
And also, this might be more for a vocational school or college, but I was super interested in hair and makeup. I really loved makeup, you see.
So I looked into vocational schools for hair and makeup. I don't know all the details, but many schools teach both hair and makeup together. I love makeup, but I'm absolutely terrible at hair styling.
I can't even do my own hair, let alone someone else's. My hands are just so clumsy.
So, even though I really wanted to go, I figured it'd probably be impossible for me.
So I gave up on it.
Oh, I just thought, 'I probably can't do this.'
Yeah, I was super interested, but even now, I still love makeup!
Thank you so much!
Um, yeah, keep up the great work!
Let's do our best together!
Next up, Happy Na-