That's right.
Thank you!
Something kinda surprising happened.
Alright, so from now on, I'd like to introduce some messages from our listeners!
First up, we got a message from Happy Name Eyal-san!
Thank you so much!
Good evening, Date-chan!
Good evening!
I'm a fan from overseas, and I'm studying Japanese.
I look forward to hearing Sayuri-san's voice every week.
I really love your radio show and the fun segments.
Thank you!
I'm a grad student in a doctoral program, researching new cancer treatments and therapies using AI.
This research is really rewarding, and I'm enjoying it a lot.
I have something I'd like to ask you, Sayuri-san.
If you were to go to university after high school, what field would you want to study?
That's what they asked!
Thank you!
Wow, from overseas! Thank you so much!
Thanks for listening!
I'm so happy! Are you doing okay?
Am I speaking proper Japanese, I wonder?
You don't need to learn words like 'yabai,' you know.
Yeah, you don't have to remember phrases like 'yabai' or 'yabai jan'.
But, uh,
Keep up the good work!
I'm rooting for you!
Wow, cancer treatments and therapies using AI!
That's amazing!
Well, I actually didn't go to university, but when I was in my first and second year of high school, you know,
I was interested in going to a university for psychology. My future dreams were still vague back then, I wasn't dead set on one thing. But I really wanted to be a school counselor, you know!
Yeah, I was interested in that around my first and second year of high school. When you look up 'school counselor,' it always says you need to study psychology. So I vaguely thought it'd be nice to study something like that back then.
But you never know, right?
Even if you decide to become a school counselor and go into psychology, you might suddenly find another path interesting while you're in university. I know a lot of people around me who were thinking of going into psychology. I feel like psychology is a pretty broad field.
At least when I looked into it.
Yeah.
And also, I was super interested in hair and makeup, maybe at a university or vocational school. I really loved makeup, you see.
So I looked into vocational schools for hair and makeup. I don't know all the details, but many schools teach both hair and makeup together. I love makeup, but I'm absolutely terrible at hair styling.
I can't even do my own hair, let alone someone else's. My hands are just so clumsy!
So, even though I really wanted to go, I figured it was impossible for me and gave up.
Oh, I just thought, 'I can't do this.'
Yeah, I was super interested, but even now, I still love makeup!
Thank you so much!
Uh, yeah, keep up the great work!
Let's do our best together!
Alright, next up, Happy Name...